t-mobile.net 2017-02-15

# Deutsche Telekom: Privacy policy

Deutsche Telekom

  * __Share __Share

Two clicks for more data privacy: click here to activate the button and send your recommendation. Data will be transfered as soon as the activation occurs.

Data protection and data security for customers and users have a high priority for the entire Deutsche Telekom Group. We therefore attach great importance to the protection of personal data in all business processes. More about our privacy policy principles, which apply to the whole DT-Group, can be found in the [ __Binding Corporate Rules Privacy (pdf, 167.0 KB)](/resource/blob/323318/7dc2556f11e7330d66953ea352662515/dl-binding-corporate-rules-privacy-data.pdf "Binding Corporate Rules Privacy") of Deutsche Telekom.

This privacy statement explains what kind of information is collected at the Deutsche Telekom Group during a visit to one of our Web sites and how we use this information. However, this does not apply to Web sites of companies which do not belong to the Group, even if they have a link to this or any other Web site of a Deutsche Telekom AG company. Should you wish to receive information on the collection and processing of personal data at specific companies of the Deutsche Telekom Group, please contact these companies directly or use our contact form.

 **Collection and processing of personal data**  
For the purpose of system security, when you visit our Web sites, our Web server temporarily registers the domain name or the [IP](/en/glossary#glossar381622) address of the requesting computer as well as the date of access, the file request of the client (file name and URL), the HTTP response code and the Web site from which you are visiting us, and the number of bytes transferred during the session. We might also, in some cases, store some information in the form of 'cookies' on your PC so that we can optimize our Web site according to your preferences. We will not collect any other personal data such as name, address, telephone number or e-mail address unless you provide this information voluntarily, e.g., when placing an online order for a product or service, a survey, a competition, or a request for information. Personal data collected during a visit to our Web site is processed exclusively in accordance with the legal provisions of the country in which the respective company is headquartered.

 **Use and forwarding of personal data**  
We will use your personal data exclusively for the technical administration of the Web site and to meet your wishes and requests. Only in cases in which you have given us prior consent do we also use this data for product-related surveys and marketing purposes, but only to the extent needed in each specific case. We will not disclose any data to government agencies except where required by law. Our employees and business offices are obligated to treat the data as confidential.

 **Data control with the[social media](/en/glossary#glossar381638) plug-ins used**  
Some of our web sites contain buttons from [social media](/en/glossary#glossar381638) networks, with which you can recommend Deutsche Telekom's offers to your friends and acquaintances. To ensure that you have full data control, when you load the page, images of the respective functions (Facebook “Like” button, Google +1, Twitter button) are displayed instead of the actual [social media](/en/glossary#glossar381638) plug-ins. The exchange of data is not activated until you click the checkmark next to the images, which loads the respective [social media](/en/glossary#glossar381638) plug-ins. When you click a plug-in to activate it, the following data may be transmitted to the website operator:

\- Your [IP](/en/glossary#glossar381622) address  
– Browser information and operating system  
\- Screen resolution  
– Installed browser plug-ins, such as Adobe Flash player  
– Origin of visitors if you followed a link (referrer)  
– URL of the current page

You can revoke your consent for the social plug-ins to be displayed on this page in future by resetting the checkmark. When you call up the next page, an image will again be displayed in the place of active [social media](/en/glossary#glossar381638) plug-ins (the checkmark is removed), and no data is forwarded.

 **Customer's decision**  
The companies of Deutsche Telekom AG like to contact customers to provide them with information about special offers and news on products and services. If you register on our Web site or place an order for our products and services, you will be asked to indicate whether you would like to receive advertising information directly. Irrespective of your consent, it goes without saying that, as a Deutsche Telekom customer, you will continue to be notified of any important changes relating to existing service agreements (e.g., rate changes).

 **Freedom of information**  
Upon written request, the respective company of the Deutsche Telekom Group will inform you of the personal data stored on you (e.g., name, address).

 **Security**  
We have taken extensive technical and operational precautions to protect the personal data retained by us against unauthorized access and misuse. Our security procedures are revised regularly and adapted to reflect technological progress.

 **Contacts**  
Should you wish any data to be corrected or deleted, or have any other questions or suggestions on data protection, please use our [ contact form](/en/contact "Contact").
